

Christchurch, New Zealand

📕 (+64) 027-210-6930 | 🔀 contact@eriherrera.com | 🛅 eriherrera

"Placed in between organisations and technology, I am committed and enthusiastic in what I do. Driven by great challenges and learning opportunities, I look forward to combining technical knowledge with interpersonal skills."

Summary.

I am Erika, a learner-centred and goal-oriented Learning Designer. With a strong background in Occupational Health & Safety and Quality control, I bring a unique perspective to learning design and project management. My work is driven by the values of continuous learning, integrity, and adaptability, ensuring effective and engaging learning experiences.

Work Experience

University of Canterbury

Christchurch, New Zealand

INSTRUCTIONAL DESIGNER Jan. 2022 - Present

- Develop engaging and innovative learning experiences from micro-credentials to undergraduate and postgraduate online certificates, integrating pedagogical expertise and evidence-based practices in blended and online learning.
- Ensure constructive alignment between the accredited curriculum, learning outcomes, and assessment items.
- · Collaborate with stakeholders to create engaging, student-centred learning experiences suitable for blended and online delivery, ensuring timely completion within scope.
- · Collaborate with the educational media production team to develop engaging visual learning resources by contributing innovative ideas, offering constructive feedback, and ensuring alignment with learning goals.
- Embrace and implement Māori Strategy and uphold the principles of Te Tiriti o Waitangi, fostering inclusivity, participation, and recognition within the learning community.

Hellers Ltd. Christchurch, New Zealand

Jul. 2019 - Jan. 2022

- Applied interaction design and interactive learning principles to instructional solutions.
- Developed training resources for on-job-trainers in collaboration with subject-matter experts (SMEs).
- Facilitated the company induction programme.
- Ensured integrity of the Safety Operating Procedures (SOPs).
- Created and managed e-learning content using video editing and multimedia techniques.
- Ensured staff were competent, productive, and supported in their work-place.
- Created and maintained databases to track staff performance.

Bodegas Grupo Peñaflor HEALTH AND SAFETY TECHNICIAN

TRAINING OFFICER

Mendoza, Argentina Feb. 2018 - Jul. 2018

• Examined credentials and work permits to ensure compliance with licensing requirements

- Supplied, controlled, and maintained personal protective equipment
- Helped direct rescue and firefighting operations in the event of a fire
- Planed emergency response drills
- Designed and facilitated training to employees and contractors

Bodegas Chandon

Mendoza, Argentina

HEALTH AND SAFETY ANALYST Jan. 2013 - Apr. 2014

- · Provided specialised training and support for implementing the key components of the H&S strategy
- Collected data and developed reports on the management of critical risk
- Designed and facilitated training to employees and contractors
- Analyse business needs to design training solutions.

Gabriel Del Mazo High School

HEALTH AND SAFETY TEACHER

Mendoza, Argentina Nov. 2012 - Mar. 2015

• Facilitated subjects according to goals and objectives set by curriculum and school policy.

- Prepared, developed, and managed lesson plans and classroom teaching resources
- · Evaluated students' work, recording results and completing reports and profiles on student achievement

OCTOBER 28, 2024 ERIKA HERRERA · RÉSUMÉ

Education

Instituto A Priori-CEC

Mendoza, Argentina

DIPLOMA IN OCCUPATIONAL HEALTH AND SAFETY

Feb. 2006 - Dec. 2009

• NZQA Diploma Level 5

Ernesto Perez Cuesta High School

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA

Mendoza, Argentina

Mar. 1999 - Dec. 2003

Courses & Certifications _____

2024	Navigating Organisational Change, Andrea Bankier, Sheffield	Christchurch, NZ
2024	Public Speaking, Franco Pisso	Online, AR
2024	Ethnic Women Leadership, Lady Khadija Trust	Christchurch, NZ
2023	Neurodiversity as a PRISM, Callum Mckirdy	Online, NZ
2023	Project Management Fundamentals, ACE Computer Training Ltd	Christchurch, NZ
2022	Te Reo Māori for the Workplace, University of Canterbury	Online, NZ
2022	Certified Articulate Storyline Advanced, B Online Learning	Online, NZ
2021	Instructional Design and Technology, University System of Maryland - Certified by edX	Online, NZ
2020	Health and Safety Leadership Training, Coolspring Consulting	Christchurch, NZ
2020	International English Language Testing System (IELTS), University of Canterbury	Christchurch, NZ
2019	Articulate Storyline 2 Virtual Training Expert Level, B Online Learning	Christchurch, NZ
2017	NZQA National Certificate in Occupational Health and Safety Level 3, Competenz	Christchurch, NZ
2017	OHSAS 18001: Occupational Health and Safety Audit & Certification, Universidad Tecnologica Nacional	Mendoza, AR

Skills

Tools Microsoft Office, Moodle, Articulate 360, Adobe Creative Cloud Applications, Jira, Monday.com

Interpersonal Teamwork, Leadership, Empathy, Motivation, Active listening

Languages Spanish, English

Publications

• Farley, H., & Herrera, E. (2023). Unlocking empathy and preparedness: Enhancing criminal justice education with Virtual Reality. *ASCILITE Publications*, 393–397. https://doi.org/10.14742/apubs.2023.578

Additional Information _____

Portfolio Available upon request **References** Available upon request